MOUNICA GADI

75 Saint Alphonsus St, Apt 0209, Boston, MA 02120 • 617-586-9058 • gadi.m@husky.neu.edu https://www.linkedin.com/in/mounicagadi • Available : May 2016 – Aug 2016

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A passionate and energetic computer science graduate with strong organizational, logical, technical and analytical skills. Ability to being adaptive by working in dynamic environments and boasting 18+ months of rich experience in the field of information technology with waterfall and agile methodologies.

EDUCATION

Northeastern University, Boston, MA

Sep 2015 – present

Expected graduation: Aug 2017

College of Computer Science and Information Science Candidate for Master of Science in Computer Science

Related Courses: Programming Design Paradigm, Information Retrieval, Web Development, Managing Software Development

Osmania University, Hyderabad

Oct 2010-May 2014

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science and Engineering

Related Courses: Database Management, Software Engineering, Algorithms, Web Development, Data Structures

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming: Python, C#, JAVA, C/C++, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, XML, Bootstrap, AngularJS

Operating Systems: Windows(98/XP/Vista/7/8/10), Unix/Linux, MS DOS

DataBases: Microsoft SQL Server 2008, Oracle Toad

Tools: Visual Studio, PyCharm, NetBeans, Eclipse, Git, SVN, JIRA, Confluence, WebStorm, MS Office,

HP Quality Center

WORK EXPERIENCE

S&P Global Market Intelligence, Hyderabad, India

June 2014-Aug 2015

Quality Analyst

- Reduced manual interference by about 40% with automation of Test Scripts.
- Cut down turn around time of database testing of Financial Project Modules such as QuantHouse, Tullett and Moody's by a quarter.
- SQL Querying to periodically synchronize technical data with Business rules which saved one full time employee of the organization.
- Implemented **desktop application in C#** for auto-execution of Stored Procedures in **SQL Server**.

${\bf S\&P~Global~Market~Intelligence},~{\bf Hyderabad},~{\bf India}$

Dec 2013-May 2014

Intern, Auto Triggering System Project

- Implemented an application in C# which enabled the automated execution of Test Scripts stored in the repository(SVN Tortoise) or on the local file system reducing manual intervention.
- Developed it using libraries of tools such as Jenkins, HP QC & SVN Tortoise.

Progress Software, Hyderabad, India

May -July 2013

Summer Intern , BITS PILANI Hyderabad Campus

- Accomplishing innovative Track I Mobile device tracking using Bluetooth Technology.
- Honored with Best Project award among 15 competing ones.

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Northeastern University

EatOut:

Jan 2016 - present

- Designing a Web Application which features restaurant information such as reviews, cost, menus and location.
- Implementing the project using **REST** API's and **Mean** Stack.

Mindfulness: Jan 2016 - present

- Developing a **Android Mobile Application** which is intended to assess the psychological states of the user by putting them through a series of assessments.
- Implementing this project using **Agile** Methodologies.

WebCrawler, Search Engine:

Sep-Nov 2015

- Designed a **Web Crawler** which is 30% as effective as conventional crawlers using **Python.**
- Built a Search Engine using an inverted index and ranked the documents using BM25 Ranking algorithm using Python.